cua.com.au 2006-10-06

# Credit Union Australia: Australia's Friendliest Banking - Privacy policy

**Privacy Statement**  
For CUA and its subsidiaries namely Credicorp Insurance Pty Ltd, Credicare Health Fund Ltd, CUA Financial Planning Pty Ltd and Leisure Travel Pty Ltd

(Please note that where appropriate any reference in this statement to CUA includes its subsidiaries.)

**Introduction**

At CUA, we realise the importance of confidentiality of our members' personal information. We only collect personal information which is necessary for one of our functions or activities. We take steps to ensure that member information is not disclosed to, or accessed by, unauthorised persons. Your personal information held by CUA is available for you to access if required.

**The National Privacy Principles (NPPs)**

CUA is bound by the NPPs which are ten principles that deal with the obligations of most of the private sector (ie non-government entities) in relation to the collection, use, storage of, and access to personal information of individuals. CUA's forms and procedures are consistent with the NPP's.

**Exemptions Under The Privacy Act**

Certain exceptions apply to the general restriction on us to deal with personal information; eg 

  * We have an obligation to on-forward your Tax File Number (TFN) to the Australian Taxation Office if you provide it to us. 
  * We must provide information to an entity if we are required to by law; eg under the Social Security (Administration) Act 1999, we must provide certain information to Centrelink if they request it from us.

**Further Information**  
If you require more detailed information in relation to what sort of personal information we hold, for what purposes we hold it, how we collect, hold, use and disclose information _click here_.
